<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="OrcVillageMaster" id="30565"
    xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Kakai</name>
        <title send="false">Flame Lord</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="26.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Flame Lord Kakai:<br> 
Originally, we Orcs consisted of seven powerful tribes and reigned over the entire world. But about 2,000 years ago, we engaged in a large scale war against those despicable Elves. Of course, the superiority of our race over any other was unquestionable -- which is undoubtedly why the Elves allied themselves with those shrewd and cunning humans. Their combined treachery defeated us and drove us far from our lands. Ah, but those arrogant Elves were also betrayed by the humans and driven deep into the woods. "The hand that parries can also thrust," as the saying goes.<br> 
After the war, our people built a new home here on the <font color="LEVEL">Immortal Plateau</font>, which was once Pa'agro's sacred ground, and we have been steadily preparing to reclaim our former glory. But <font color="LEVEL">the Ragna Tribe</font>, one of the seven original tribes, betrayed the rest. Their shameful act has tainted our people's honor. It is unforgivable! they do not even deserve to be called "Orcs."<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Go back.</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Flame Lord Kakai:<br>
Hear me! I am Flame Lord Kakai, invested with the authority of Pa'agrio, the father of eternal flame, to lead the great Orc race. Young warrior, you are to my eyes like a flame of hope, hope that our race may yet achieve its former glory. What do you wish from me?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest 30565_kakai_occupation_change">Listen to information about second class transfer.</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about the current situation</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest 9000_clan">Clan</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest 9001_alliance">Alliance</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
