<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="Guard" id="30726" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="true" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Tebose</name>
        <title send="false">Guard</title>
        <level>80</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="8.5" max="3290.11306877694"/>
            <mp regen="3.0" max="1674.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="970.53755"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="662.75133"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="341.375"/>
                <magical value="249.80341"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <item lefthand="20" righthand="2"/>
        <collision heigth="24.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Tebose:<br>
If you leave through this door and head south you'll arrive at Oren Castle and the town of Oren. Have you come from the south? If so, I've told you useless information. Would you like to know about the Ivory Tower?<br>
I know a secret about the tower... A close Mystic friend of mine told me when he was drunk and the next day he vanished from the tower. How about it, are you still curious?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about the Ivory Tower.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Ask how he is still alive.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_TerritoryStatus">See the Lord and get the tax rate information.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Tebose:<br>
Shhh! Who knows... Many have heard this story besides you. I know, it sounds crazy... But if I vanish like my friend, will anyone notice? Maybe that is why I'm still alive?<br>
Or, perhaps everything I said was nonsense and my friend got drunk and went to the Tower of Oman to look at the stars...<br>
And you, what do you think?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Tebose:<br>
The thing is, these craters around the Ivory Tower were made by shooting stars a long time ago. The Ivory Tower was created by Mages who knew the mysterious power of extinguihed stars.<br>
The Elmoraden Empire was governed by Mages who harnessed the power of these stars, but as time passed the power ebbed and the influence of the Ivory Tower grew weaker. Then, 50 years ago, a Great Wizard began experimenting with the power of shooting stars. However his work was incomplete, and the Mages have yet to regain anything resembling their former power. Consequently, many strange creatures have taken up residence around the tower.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
