<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="Guard" id="30875" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="true" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Carlton</name>
        <title send="false">Guard</title>
        <level>80</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="8.5" max="3290.11306877694"/>
            <mp regen="3.0" max="1674.8"/>
            <attack critical="8" evasion="0" range="1100">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="970.53755"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="662.75133"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="341.375"/>
                <magical value="249.80341"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="160.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <item lefthand="0" righthand="275"/>
        <collision heigth="24.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Carlton:<br>
Well... There's tairim... It's like a bundle of fire that just floats around in the air... The undead called by the grand name of marsh judge... The giant rats called tulben.. You know about gargoyles, right? The marsh stalkers are also very dangerous. But the most threatening thing is the marsh drake. It's similar to other drakes but comes attacking with fire...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Go back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Carlton:<br>
The swamp to the north of Aden Castle is called the Blazing Swamp. The name makes one think of some hellish sea of fire that is covered in molten rock or something... But looking at it from the outside, it really doesn't seem much different than any other marsh. However, the monsters that come out of it are a bit peculiar. Paagrio did something there... And so they are all masters of the fire line of magic... King Raoul gave the order that a waterway be dug at the edge of the marsh to prevent the spreading of fires to the area around. But the most famous thing about the Blazing Swamp happened when King Amadeo was attacked by Elmore... Oh, right. It wouldn't be good for you to know about this long-winded story.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about monsters.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
