<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.NotImplementedNPCController"
    id="31340" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Mathias</name>
        <title send="false">Captain</title>
        <level>80</level>
        <race>HUMAN</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="8.5" max="3290.11306877694"/>
            <mp regen="3.0" max="1674.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="970.53755"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="662.75133"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="341.375"/>
                <magical value="249.80341"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <item lefthand="632" righthand="133"/>
        <collision heigth="23.5" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Captain Mathias:<br>
Welcome, traveler, to the capital of the kingdom of Elmore. You must be tired from your long journey. May your time in our fair city be restful and relaxing.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about Kamaloka.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Look at the list of Kamaloka</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest Kamaloka">Enter Kamaloka.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">"Do you know anything about the ominous rumor I heard?"</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_TerritoryStatus">Ask about the local lord and tax rate.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>
Kamaloka is an invader from another world. We do not know precisely when it happened, but we discovered a sealed space, similar to a Dimensional Rift. We call it Kamaloka.<br>
To enter it, you must meet certain requirements. You cannot enter a basic Kamaloka alone. If you wish to fight alone, find the Pathfinders who can lead you to a Rim Kamaloka.<br>
On the other hand, there is an upper limit to how many can enter. More than 6 characters cannot enter it. <br>
You should also be well-rested before entering. According to the priests, it requires a similar amount of energy as entering the Sealed Dimension. Unless your soul is well rested, you will not be allowed in.<br>
Each Kamaloka possesses a certain level; only characters near that level may enter. <br>
There are also several kinds of Kamaloka. Even if they appear to be the same Kamaloka or Near Kamaloka, they are divided into several patterns. So far, two distinct patterns have been identified: Hall and Labyrinth. You may only enter the Hall type now, and soon you will be able to enter the Labyrinth. <br>
(In real time, you can enter a regular Kamaloka and Near Kamaloka once per day. You need 3000 PC cafe points in order to enter the Near Kamaloka.) <br>
(Only characters whose levels are 5 levels higher or lower than the Kamaloka's levels may enter.)
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>
Researchers at the Ivory Tower believe that Kamaloka is a result of another dimension overlapping Aden. The monsters of Kamaloka are tremendously powerful. Adventurers must take care to enter only the Kamaloka appropriate for their level.<br>
The following captains can grant access:<br>
Captain Bathis (Town of Gludio): Level 23, 26, 29<br>
Captain Lucas (Town of Dion): Level 33, 36, 39<br>
Captain Gosta (Heine): Level 43, 46, 49<br>
Captain Mouen (Town of Oren): Level 53, 56, 59<br>
Captain Vishotsky (Town of Schuttgart) Level 63, 66, 69<br>
Captain Mathias (Town of Rune): Level 73, 78, 81
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="4"><![CDATA[<html><body>Captain Mathias:<br>
People shouldn't spread false rumors! I've heard them all before... devil worshippers , vampires, blah blah blah... The ravings of drunks! This town is well-protected by our royal guards! Don't worry! Who is spreading these lies? If you hear anyone saying such rubbish, tell me immediately! I know you wouldn't be so stupid as to do it! The rich people in this town take a very dim view of such groundless fearmongering! If I were you, I'd watch what I say!<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="14" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
