<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<template:npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.NotImplementedNPCController"
    id="30877" xsi:schemaLocation="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:template="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc">
    <info aggressive="true" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Grayson</name>
        <title send="false">Guard</title>
        <level>80</level>
        <race>HUMAN</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="8.5" max="3290.11306877694"/>
            <mp regen="3.0" max="1674.8"/>
            <attack critical="8" evasion="0" range="1100">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="970.53755"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="662.75133"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="341.375"/>
                <magical value="249.80341"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="160.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <item lefthand="0" righthand="275"/>
        <collision heigth="24.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Grayson:<br>
Are you a traveler? Why have you come to Aden Castle Town? You're not actually planning on going to the Shilen Holy Place to the east of the National Cemetary, are you? If you're intending to go there, I'll need to investigate various matters about you here.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Say that you are going to the Shilen Holy Place.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Say that you don't have any interest in the Shilen Holy Place.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Grayson:<br>
No, it's nothing special. It's just the useless chatter of crazy fanatics. It has been said that, a long time ago, when Shilen caused a war against Einhasad and lost, for some reason, the gods didn't kill Shilen but rather sealed her into the location that we are speaking of now...<br>
The book called the Scriptures of the Seal lists seven methods of releasing the seal of Shilen. And this is not just the seven ghost stories that are spoken of by children in school...<br>
Ah, if the depraved god is resurrected, the people living in the land will all die so do you really think that the sealing would have been done so carelessly? Obviously, this is just the useless talk of a crazy person. And if it is so easy to resurrect, the depraved goddess would have already resurrected in the distant past... Do you think that lady would still be sleeping like this if she had any choice? Am I right?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Go back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Grayson:<br>
Hmm. OK, that's a good thing. There are rumors that some suspicious adventurers have come and gone from there so I'm guarding against that especially. As there are a lot of crazy people around, you can't ever relax. Regardless of whether it's because of the <br>
<font color="LEVEL">Scriptures of the Seal</font> or whatever, there's always a lot going on.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">Ask about the Scriptures of the Seal.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Guard Grayson:<br>
Is that a fact? OK then, wait a moment. First I need to record your belongings and appearance. And what's your name?<br>
....?<br>
.... What kind of a name is that? Alright, fine. If you're really planning to go to the Shilen Holy Place, then there are some things I need to notify you about.<br>
You might already know about this but that place is where the depraved god Shilen gave birth to six dragons and then changed them into death goddesses. According to the legend, the army of light defeated the depraved god but was not able to kill the goddesses that control the world of darkness and so they are sealed in that place. Therefore, there are a lot of religious researchers, clergymen and fanatics gathered there...<br>
And there are strange ones that want to kill not just the Dark Elves that serve Shilen but also those that serve the god of light, as well as other gods, which they regard as being cults. The crazy ones that fight saying they will release the seal of Shilen have plenty to do... And there are many watchers sent by the religious bodies in order to stop all those blasphemous ones. These watchers are in utter dissolutionment because of the depravity of this age... Therefore, I'm entreating you that if you go there, please avoid any actions which could have any chance of being misunderstood. I mean, regardless of whether they are fanatics of Shilen or watchers of the seal... OK?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Go back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="9" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="14" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</template:npc>
