<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<template:npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.impl.SimpleNPCController"
    id="30602" xsi:schemaLocation="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc ../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:template="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Newbie Guide</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>ORC</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="27.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="6"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
Several of the villagers here could use your help. Talk to them and click on<font color="LEVEL"> Quest</font> to see what missions they have to offer.<br>
Of course, even if they're looking for help they're not going to offer you a mission that's beyond your capabilities. If they refuse to offer you anything, it means you need to get some more experience first. Nobody wants you to get into trouble you can't get out of.<br>
And remember - some quests can only be completed once, but others can be completed several times.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 7">I want to know more about quests.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="12"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
The Newbie Travel Token is reserved for players of level 20 or below.<br>
It allows the player to move to the start town of another tribe via the<font color="LEVEL"> Newbie Guides</font> in each town<br>
Be cautionus, for in many cases, you may learn and practice certain skills and quests that are unique to the own of each tribe.<br>
Once a player reaches level 20, he is no longer able to teleport using the Newbie Travel Token.
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
It's never too early to think about your long-term goals. The Kingdom of Aden is in chaos, because they are at war with Elmore to the north and Gracia across the sea. Remember,<font color="LEVEL"> there are alwyas opportunities during times of chaos. You're just a novice grunt now, but it's your duty to become a great hero and restore the Orc race to supremacy.<br>
You must begin by familiarizing yourself with the gear you already have. Whether you seek to become a dragon slayer or the commander of a great horde of Orcs, it all begins with your training here.<br>
Start out by hunting crimson keltirs or kasha wolves around the village. When you find items left behind by the monsters you slay, try equipping the armour and weapons, to see if they're better than what you already have. If you have no other use for them, you can always sell them at a shop.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="4"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
For now, go out and hunt<font color="LEVEL"> crimson keltirs</font>, elder crimson keltirs or kasha wolves northwest of the village. Wolves are the most dangerous, so watch out. Leave the village by the north or south gate and climb down the hill. You can't miss them.<br>
When you target a monster, the monster's name appears in the upper central portion of the screen.<font color="LEVEL"> The colour of the name tells you the monster's difficulty</font>. For now, hunt those that appear in white or sky blue. Those that appear in red or yellow are much stronger than you, so leave them alone.<br>
And I warn you, don't try to tangle with the goblins yet. Goblins are smarter and stronger than you think, but the most dangerous thing is that they know about teamwork. If you attack one, several others may come to its aid. Even if you might have a chance against a single goblin, you won't be able to stand against two or three.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="5"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
You can begin to learn skills when you reach level 5. You will recieve instruction in new skills at the Warrior Guild, which is the room on the right when you enter the House of the King, the biggest building in the village, right in the center of town. The prefects there will teach you your skills.<br>
Now, pay attention; you'll need<font color="LEVEL"> SP</font> to gain your skills. SP is short for "skill points", and they're earned along with the experience whenever you defeat a monster. SP are deducted whenever you learn a new skill. You can check your SP by clicking the Character Status button, then on the Status tab in the window. Of course, the number of SP you need will vary, depending on the skill you're after.<br>
If you use your head while hunting, you should have about 60 SP by the time you reach level 5. The prefects can tell you the skills in which you can train.<br>
Skills are divided into active skills and passive skills.<font color="LEVEL"> Active skills</font> require that you intentionally use them, while passive skills increase your basic abilities from the moment you learn them. At level 5, you'll want to learn active offensive skills first. Power Strike is for those who fight with a sword, Iron Fist for hand-to-hand Fighters.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
You wish to grow strong and powerful, Eh? Then listen carefully; I will advice you!<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask for advice.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest NpcLocationInfo">NPC Location Information.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/BlessingOfProtection.htm">Receive blessing of protection.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 12">Ask about the Newbie Travel Token.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest 1104_NewbieTravelToken">Teleport using the Newbie Travel Token.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/SupportMagic.htm">Receive help from beneficial magic.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest NewbieCoupons">Ask for help with a newbie item.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
I suppose you're using the weapons and armor you were issued by the Priests of Paagrio, That's unless you have rich friends, of course, eh?<br>
Whatever you have is fine for now. Remember to pay attention to what you find while hunting monsters - you can find armour, and sometimes even weapons, in the wild. If you're lucky, you might find<font color="LEVEL"> cloth shoes, apprentice's shoes, or a cloth cap</font>.<br>
You should have been given two weapons, a squire's sword and training gloves. Even a novice like you can tell the difference between a sword and a brawling weapon, I think. The<font color="LEVEL"> training gloves (hand-to-hand weapon)</font> hit twice as often as other weapons, but they're not as powerful. Plus, you need both hands, so forget about a shield. Now the squire's sword (one-handed sword) is much sower than the gloves, but is more accurate and does more damage. Remember that different weapons may call upon different skills in their use. Either is a worth weapon - it is up to you to decide which suits you best.<br>
Come back when you reach<font color="LEVEL"> level 6</font> and we'll talk more about weapons.
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
What do you want me to teach you first? A novice like you is pretty ignorant, but we can fix that. Just listen to what I have to teach.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">What should I do now?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">What is the best equipment for me?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">What is the best hunting site for me?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 5">Tell me about skills</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 6">Which quests are available to me?</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="7"><![CDATA[<html><body> 
I'll tell you about any quests I hear of, but I don't know everything. You should talk with all the villagers you can.<br>
Have you met<font color="LEVEL"> Praetorian Rukain</font>, who guards the north gate of the village? He often asks novice Fighters to prove their valor as Orcs. If you're feeling brave, give it a try.<br>
And you can go to the House of the King, the big building in the center of the village. The room on the left as you enter is the Shaman's Guild<font color="LEVEL"> Seer Livina</font> there has a problem with goblin thieves, I heard. Why don't you see if she could use your help?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="17" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</template:npc>
