<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<template:npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.impl.SimpleNPCController"
    id="30949" xsi:schemaLocation="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc ../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:template="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Keplon</name>
        <title send="false">Researcher</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>DWARVEN</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="19.7" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="4"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Keplon:<br> 
It permits teleportation between the floors of the tower. I'm not sure exactly how it works, but through much trial and error I have determined how to go to the first, fifth and tenth floor.<br> 
To go to the <font color="LEVEL">fifth floor</font>, you need a <font color="LEVEL">Blue Dimension Stone</font>.<br> 
These are quite rare... At great personal cost I was able to secure a small box of them, but Hallate and his minions stole them away... Now they can only be obtained by killing those demons... <br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">"Tell me more about Death Lord Hallate."</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Keplon:<br> 
Don't you get it?! This tower is itself a battleground! I don't know what is on the top floor, only that there are many who seek it. Worst among them are <font color="LEVEL"> Death Lord Hallate and his legion</font>. Hallate is responsible for the destruction of the force field that once protected the tower. <br>The <font color="LEVEL">Platinum tribe</font> and <font color="LEVEL">angels</font>  have guarded the tower for hundreds of years, but recently have been driven from the lower levels by Hallate and his minions. Thankfully they still control the upper floors...<br> 
You mustn't think of these guardians as our allies, however. To them we are just more invaders to be dealt with. Above all, remember to avoid looking directly into the eyes of Death Lord Hallate and his minions!<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Keplon:<br> 
Such arrogance! Young people these days...tsk tsk... anyway...<br> 
I am a researcher from the Gray Pillar Guild, sent to study the Tower of Insolence. It is considered the greatest architectural achievement of all time. There are many secrets here yet to be revealed. <br> 
If you are going to ignore my advice and stay here, I would like to ask you for a favor: When I came to this place I was accompanied by two other researchers... While they were investigating the <font color="LEVEL">dimension vortex</font> they vanished! If you find them please tell them that if they want to reach the <font color="LEVEL">10th floor</font> they should use a <font color="LEVEL">Red Dimension Stone</font>...<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">"What is the secret of the tower?"</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">"What is a dimension vortex?"</a></body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Keplon:<br> 
Have you any idea of the danger all around you? Carelessness will kill you!<br> 
You should go back to the village immediately! What is the point of satisfying your curiousity if you end up dead?<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">"Then why are you here?"</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">"What makes this place so dangerous?"</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">"What is a dimension vortex?"</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Keplon:<br>
As you are no doubt aware this tower is the greatest achievement of Baium, the last king of the Elmoreden Empire. It was a feat unimaginable to even the most advanced Human architects of that time. <br>
Baium kidnapped 10 Elven architects and forced them to design this spectacular tower. When construction was complete he ordered the executions of all who worked on it, from the Elven architects all the way down to the lowliest laborer. This insured that no one would ever discover the secret of the tower.<br>
This stroke of brutal genius worked as intended. The secret has been lost for millenia. The Gray Pillar Guild became determined to unlock the secret of the tower, and dispatched a team of researchers to investigate.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="18" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</template:npc>
