<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.NotImplementedNPCController"
    id="30221" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="npc">
    <info aggressive="true" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Rayen</name>
        <title send="false">Sentinel</title>
        <level>80</level>
        <race>ELVEN</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="8.5" max="3290.11306877694"/>
            <mp regen="3.0" max="1674.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="970.53755"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="662.75133"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="341.375"/>
                <magical value="249.80341"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="160.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <item lefthand="0" righthand="130"/>
        <collision heigth="23.5" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Sentinel Rayen:<br>
If you cross this bridge and travel along the road southwest, you will pass the abandoned underground fortress and the Neutral Zone, and arrive at the place that the Humans call Gludio.<br>
Gludio is the largest region in the Human Kingdom of Aden. However, it was attacked by another Human Kingdom called Gracia from overseas a few years ago, so parts of the region have burned down. Since history began, Humans have always enjoyed cruel wars in this way.<br>
The war has left many ruins in Gludio, which have become dangerous places haunted by the undead. Also, huge insects lurk in the vast wastelands in the south. As it is, if you decide to go there, you must be fully prepared before you leave.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Sentinel Rayen:<br>
May the wind of the forest lead you to peace. I am the sentinel Rayen. Our duty is to drive away those who try to attack our forest and village.<br>
The Elven Forest is no doubt our home. However, we have lived in the seclusion of this forest too long and I believe that living our lives isolated from the outside world has made us weak. I advise Elves who have learned the basics of sword and spell to go out beyond the forest into the land of Humans and extend their knowledge. The first gateway would be <font color="LEVEL">Gludio</font>, located to the south of the Elven Forest.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about Gludio.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_TerritoryStatus">View the Lord and get the tax rate information.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="16" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="15" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
