<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="Merchant" id="30892" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Enverun</name>
        <title send="false">Accessory Merchant</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="24.0" radius="10.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Trader Enverun:<br>
Welcome, youngster. Our shop offers both magic items and more mundane supplies. We cater to not only magicians, but also to warriors seeking protection against magic -- and even ladies looking for pretty accessories... So many people come to our shop! We even have adventurers seeking clues to the location of the <font color="LEVEL">Sword of Othelotte</font> in some of our ancient spellbooks... They must think this is a blasted library!<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Buy 3089200">Buy/Sell/Refund.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Buy 3089202">Buy/Sell/Refund Common Items.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_TerritoryStatus">Ask about the local lord and tax rate.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about the Sword of Othelotte.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Trader Enverun:<br>
What, you haven't heard? Is this your first visit to Innadril? The Sword is the symbol of the Lord of Innadril. It is filled with history. Several decades ago, the water dragon Fafurion rose up and caused great devastation in these parts. Then Lionel, the hunter, he was just a young lad at that time...well, he faced the dragon -- without armor, mind you -- and somehow put the dragon to sleep. The Goddess Eva was so thankful that she gave him a magic sword. In the years that followed, it became the symbol for the Lord of Innadril. That is the <font color="LEVEL">Sword of Othelotte</font>.<br>
But recently the sword has disappeared... No one, not even the lord himself, nkows its whereabouts. And now Giran is scuttling its trade agreements with us, claiming that without the sword there is no rightful lord in Innadril and the treaties are invalidated... Those treacherous merchants!<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="pk"><![CDATA[<html><body>Trader Enverun:<br>
Hey, you! Get out of my store! You'll drive away my respectable customers! Get out!
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
