<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="30539" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Chichirin</name>
        <title send="false">Priestess of the Earth</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>DWARVEN</race>
        <sex>FEMALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="18.0" radius="7.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Priestess of the Earth Chichirin:<br>
<font color="LEVEL">Earth Wyrm Trasken</font> was one of the wicked devils created by <font color="LEVEL">Shilen</font>, the goddess of darkness and death. Long ago, when Shunaiman, the king of Elmoreden, was building the Seal of Shilen, Earth Worm Trasken escaped from King Shunaiman, the tales tell us. It is said that Trasken settled here, and was sleeping deep within the Spine Mountains, where we live now.<br>
So our ancestors, who had no idea about the sleeping Trasken, made a tragic mistake, and awoke the Earth Worm while collecting mithril. That devil, newly roused from deep slumber, was too powerful for the armies of the Dwarves. The Earth Worm destroyed the village and killed Dwarves mercilessly.<br>
We Dwarves were about to be massacred! However, Hero Lucien, who was born with the blessing of Maphr, suddenly appeared with his people! <font color="LEVEL">Carna Maphr!</font> Praise the goddess -- she did not abandon us! Hero Lucien defeated the wicked Earth Worm with his fighting skills and divine courage.<br>
But listen, for this must always be remembered! Although Earth Worm Trasken has died, <font color="LEVEL">Trasken's egg</font> is still alive somewhere deep in the Spine Mountains. Shilen's followers are, even now, trying to revive the Earth Worm. <font color="LEVEL">Carna Maphr</font> We must arm ourselves with faith and train harder to prepare for that day!
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Priestess of the Earth Chichirin:<br>
<font color="LEVEL">Carna Maphr!</font> May the blessing of the Goddess of the Earth be with you.<br>
The venerated <font color="LEVEL">Hero Lucien</font> had enormous strength and willpower when he fought against the wicked <font color="LEVEL">Earth Wyrm Trasken,</font> saving us Dwarves from the evil creature. Lucien once said, "I, Lucien, have always believed that the Goddess of the Earth is forever with me. Today s victory was only possible because of the blessing of the Goddess of the Earth!" What a wise remark!<br>
We can learn a valuable lesson from Lucien, only those who truly believe in the Goddess's bounty will find what they seek!<br>
<font color="LEVEL">Carna Maphr,</font> I'm sure that you too will be blessed if you keep true to your faith.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about the Earth Wyrm.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="18" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
