<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="30703" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Colin</name>
        <title send="false">Guild President</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="23.0" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Hunters Guild Member Colin:<br>
Hey, you look familiar! What brings you to the Hunters Guild?<br>
Are you here to join the guild? Well, we aren't accepting any new members. Or could it be that you are here for something else? Ask anything, I will attempt to answer your questions with the utmost respect.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Tell me about the Hunters Guild.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Tell me about the geographical features of the village.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">Where is a good place to hunt?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Hunters Guild Member Colin:<br>
The Hunters Guild is a brotherhood of extraordinary Hunters. We are professionals, constantly honing our skills... We hunt prey never imaginated by tipical hunters... You will know the details soon...<br>
the Hunters Guild is a somewhat autonomous. Even though Castle Aden has dispatched Guards, we are capable of defending ourselves. The Guards are aware of this and even approve, but our town stubbornly insist that the Guards stay here...<br>
It is a somewhat complicated story...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Hunters Guild Member Colin:<br>
The most wonderful place around here is the Enchanted Valley! If you leave town on the northwest road, you will get there right away. The scenery is wonderful and you will find many kinds of unique game. Even though our union has priority hunting privileges, we don't stop others from hunting. However, it can be quite a challenging place to hunt...<br>
The Forest of Mirrors is located to the east and Dragon Valley to the south. Both places are as dangerous as the Enchanted Valley. If you are interested you should go there... But be careful! I don't want to have to retrieve your corpse!<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Hunters Guild Member Colin:<br>
The town's geographical features? Oh my... Lazy aren't you? Have you no legs?<br>
Well, as you already probably know, the town is to the northwest, and the southeast... It is divided into two large areas like this. The shops are lined up above, and several guilds are situated on the bottom. These two areas are divided by a large canyon, and if you happen to fall into it you will have a hard time climbing back up. So be carefull<br>
There are two bridges that connect the north and south part of town. In the past, the King accused us being of being bandits. When he came to subjugate us, my grandfather and father disabled the two bridges and fought for over three months until the King gave up. It was Duke Athebalt who finally made peace between the Hunters Guild and the King.<br>
Certainly you are aware that the son of the Duke is a Guild Master in our town. I'm speaking of Aren! He is a great guy, even though he is noble birth...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
