<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="30735" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Sophya</name>
        <title send="false">Mercenary Captain</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>HUMAN</race>
        <sex>FEMALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="21.5" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Mercenary Captain Sophya:<br>
In the northwest part of the Cruma Marshlands, the marsh stakatos are building their power base.  In the northeast part, the exiled ol mahum partisans are encampred.<br>
On top of that Enku orcs, tumran bugbears, and delu lizerdmen are waiting for an easy opportunity to plunder the village. Nightly the undead stream out of the Execution Grounds to the east.<br>
It seems we are surrounded by our enemies...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Mercenary Captain Sophya:<br>
Currently our 3rd platoon, the main force of our mercenary troop is fighting a important battle in Gludio against the Ol Mahum Stragglers. The 2nd platoon has been dispatched to drive out the evil spirits of the Wasteland. Captain <font color="LEVEL">Leopold</font> who is stationed in Gludin, is better informed about the details of the situation there...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Mercenary Captain Sophya:<br>
Ah, it is always such a pleasure to see a fresh-faced traveler! My name is Sophya. I command the 4th platoon of the Black Lion Mercenary Troop We have been hired by the mayor of the Town of Dion to drive away evil spirits. I fear I underestimated the number of evil spirits in this place when I took this job<br>
If you plan to travel in the vicinity of Gludio or Giran you should prepare yourself for attack from an Enku Orc or a dire wolf. You look skillful enough, I expect that you will survive.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">"Tell me about the Black Lion Mercenary Troop."</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">"Tell me about evil spirits in this area."</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="14" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
