<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="30951" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Pithgon</name>
        <title send="false">Researcher</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>DWARVEN</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="19.7" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Pithgon:<br> 
Members of the Platinum tribe resemble wolves. They may also appear somewhat similar to the ol mahums, but they worship the goddess of light. It is their sacred duty to kill any invaders who enter the Tower of Insolence. Their devotion can be quite deadly and they should be avoided when at all possible...<br> 
They are led by winged creatures known as angels... The Mystics would say that they are "spirits serving the goddess in this dimension." There are two types of angels: seal angels and guardian angels.<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Pithgon:<br> 
The dimension vortex was invented by the ancients to allow instantaneous teleportation within the tower walls.<br> 
Activation requires a dimension stone. Each floor is accessed by different colored stones. For instance, to move to the fifth floor, you need a <font color="LEVEL">Blue Dimension Stone</font>. To go to the first floor, you need a <font color="LEVEL">Green Dimension Stone</font>.<br> 
All of the dimension stones are quite rare, but especially precious are the red ones. These are favored by the Platinum tribe and their angels, and are almost impossible to obtain.<br> 
You could always take the stairs of course! The exercise might be good for your health! Or not! Heh heh!<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Return</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Researcher Pithgon:<br> 
Where did you come from? Certainly not the stairs?! Did you by any chance use the dimension vortex?<br> 
That was quite brave of you. This area is guarded by the Platinum tribe and angels. They will surely view you as a hostile invader and try to kill you. Adventure is one thing, but your life is in serious peril! You must be careful!<br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">"Tell me about the Platinum tribe and angels."</a><br> 
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">"What is the dimension vortex?"</a> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="18" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
