<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="31077" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Newbie Guide</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>HUMAN</race>
        <sex>FEMALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="20.5" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
May blessing of light be upon you! It is my responsibility to help beginning adventurers adjust.<br>
This world is getting dangerous! Violent spirits, unending wars, even this unnatural struggle between Dawn and Dusk! You will need both strength and wisdom to survive. Please remember my advice...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask for advice about class transfers.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/SupportMagic.htm">See the list of available supplemental magic.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/SupportMagicServitor.htm">See the list of supplemental magic for servitors.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/BlessingOfProtection.htm">Receive Blessing of Protection.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest NewbieCoupons">Receive support with a Newbie item.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
A class transfer permits a character who has reached a certain level of experience and ability to acquire a new, higher-level occupation.<br>
In order to complete the class transfer, you must undertake a <font color="LEVEL">Class Change Quest</font>. Only characters who are at least level 19 may perform this quest; the class transfer takes effect once the quest is completed and the character reaches level 20. Choose your new occupation wisely, because you cannot undue it once the class transfer is completed.<br>
To hear detailed information about where you can receive a Class Transfer Quest, which occupations you can choose, and more, you should speak to the appropriate Grand Master.<br>
Fighters and Elven Fighters should visit Grand Master Rains of the Fighters Guild.<br>
Mages and Elven Mages should visit High Priest Raymond of the Temple.<br>
Dark Fighters and Dark Mages should visit Grand Master Tobias of the Dark Elf Guild.<br>
Orc Fighters and Orc Mages should visit High Prefect Drikus.<br>
Dwarf Fighters should visit Warehouse Chief Rikadio or Head Blacksmith Mendio.<br>
Kamael Soldiers should visit Grand Master Gershwin of the Kamael Guild.
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="3" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="14" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
