<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="" id="31862" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Angelic Vortex</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>490</experience>
        <sp>10</sp>
        <collision heigth="35.0" radius="7.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Angelic Vortex:<br>
The Angelic Vortex emits a faint light, in the midst of which an image appears. A large, open space... but the gigantic, human-like stone statue is no longer there.<br>
It seems that while the statue is not visible, one could cross over to that place.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Ask about the stone statue.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Angelic Vortex:<br>
The Angelic Vortex emits a faint light, and in the midst of the light an image appears. In the deepest part of a specious area, a gigantic stone statue is visible. The statue has a human-like appearance and is in a seated position, as though it was being held by some invisible force against its will.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest baium">Go where the Angelic Vortex leads.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Angelic Vortex:<br>
In ancient times a mighty emperor named Baium became so enamored of his own power that he began to fancy himself a god. He conscripted all of his people to build an awesome tower that reached almost to heaven.<br>
The gods were not amused. They struck him down, cursed him with immortality and imprisoned him in his own tower for eternity! A statue of the foolish emperor stands there to this day.<br>
Occasionally, the old emperor himself is woken up by those who seek his power. Unfortunately, when Baium is disturbed, so are the angels who guard him.<br>
Although the angels are certainly no friend of Baium, they regard Humans with equal disdain. <font color="LEVEL">Ultimate success against Baium depends upon the defeat of the guardian angels.</font><br>
This is all I can tell you. Good luck!
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
