<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="32115" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Asamah</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="60.0" run="100.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="41.5" radius="45.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Asamah:<br>
You must know which action to use when a Tyrannosaurus tries to cancel a capture skill. When the beast <font color="LEVEL">roars, shakes and writhes</font>, the appropriate capture skills to use are <font color="LEVEL">kabokula, tapirawa and shabonoba</font>. Watch each action of the Tyrannosaurus carefuly and respond with the correct skill.<br>
Remember that using a capture skill consumes both capture stones and MP be sure to prepare enuogh of them both! May Shilen bless your efforts!
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Asamah:<br>
I am Asamah, son of Mushika, chief of the Elroki tribe. These are our lands. In them lies perhaps our last hope to return to our ancient ancestral home. But these days are evil, and our hope is waning before this threat.<br>
Our strength has run out like water from a broken pot, and although my ancestors would be shamed to ask foraid, I believe only an outsider like yourself can save us now.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Find out how to use the capture skill.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Buy</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Asamah:<br> 
If you have a trap, then you may use at least 3 types of capture skills. You can only use a capture skill on the predatory Tyrannosaurus.<br>
If you are capturing a Tyrannosaurus for the first time, you will use the <font color="LEVEL">Kabokula</font> technique most among the three capture skills. But you cannot completely capture this powerful predatory dinosaur with just one skill type!<br>
At this pont, watch the Tyrannosaurus reactions and use the proper skill to maintain its state of captivity. Nothing is a better teacher than your own experience, but since you have come all this way, I will tell you the traditional capture method of the Elkrohki. Listen carefuly.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Next</a><br> 
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
