<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="" id="32135" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Newbie Guide</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="20.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="25.0" radius="17.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="12"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
The Newbie Travel Token is reserved for players of level 20 or below.<br>
It allows the player to move to the start town of another tribe via the <font color="LEVEL">Newbie Guides</font> in each town.<br>
Be cautious, for in many cases, you may learn and practice certain skills and quests that are unique to the town of each tribe.<br>Once a player reaches level 20, he is no longer able to teleport using the Newbie Travel Token.
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
Can I help you with anything? What do you wish do know?<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask for advice.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest NpcLocationInfo">NPC Location Information.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 12">Ask about Newbie Travel Tokens.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest 1104_NewbieTravelToken">Teleport using Newbie Travel Token.</a><br><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Link default/SupportMagic.htm">Check the list of available Support Magic.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest NewbieCoupons">Ask for help with a newbie item.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="16"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
A<font color="LEVEL">One-Handed Blunt Weapon</font>has a higher
accuracy than other weapons, but a low Critical
 Rate. Blunt Weapons are designed to <font color="LEVEL">reliably
 cause a lot of damage</font>. I recommend them for
hunters, for example.<br>
As you advance, you can acquire skills
specifically for Blunt Weapons. Something to keep
in mind about these weapons is that they have
greader damage range than other weapon types.
They may not be particularly attractive, but they
are sturdy, reliable weapons.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
Ah! You have matured a gread deal since you last
 visit me. I am glad to see the change in you. I
 do not know if I can be of much help to you now,
 but feel free to ask.<br>
If you already know the answer I give, come
back to me after you reach lvl 11. At that time
 I will be able to give you new informatio.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">What should I do now?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">What is the best equipment for me?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">What is the best hunting site for me?</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 5">Tell me about skills</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 6">Which quests are available to me?</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="17"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
A<font color="LEVEL">Two-Handed Sword or Two-Handed Blunt
Weapon</font> possesses both formidable power and
reach compared to their one-handed
counterparts. That power comes at the price of
quickness, however.<br>
The weapons are a good choice for these who
 rely on inflicting devasting damage in combat.
 But if you wish to purchase them, you'd better
 raise your level and save your money! Of course,
 the differences specified between the
One-Handed Sword and the One-Handed Blunt
 Weapon apply to the two-handed versions as
well.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="14"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
If you have hunted well, you can equip yourself
with good armor. Otherwise, you will have to
upgrade gradually. Once you've reached level 6,
you can wear Apprentice's Shoes, Cloth Caps and
Short Gloves with your armor.<br>
If you are particularty lucky, you may acquire a 
full set of leather armors. SOme warriors think a
wapon is more important than armor, so they
only focus on buying weapons. But I think it is
better to systematically upgrade both weapons
and armor.<br>
Finally, I'll tell you about a Shield. While it
certainly can reduce the damage you take, it will
slow you down and isn't suitable for some
missions. If you have a job that requires that you
wear heavy armor, a shield is necessary. For
other jobs for which a Dagger and light armor are
better, a Shield will only be a burden<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
From now on, you must pay more attention!
Listen to me carefully: the most important thing
for you to have is the will to seek adventure in
 the depest parts of the Isle of Souls. Follow that
 will and you may feel yourself already becoming
 a stronger Kamael.<br>
Ah, one last thing! When you reach level 10, visit
 <font color="LEVEL">Hierarch Kekropus</font> and he will tell you of the test
 you must take to become a true Kameal warrior.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="4"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
At that level, you can fight the <font color="LEVEL">Green Goblin and
 Hill Werewolves</font>. If you are skilled at hunting, you
 can also fight the <font color="LEVEL">Muertos Archer</font> or <font color="LEVEL">Mountain
 Fungus.</font><br>
You can find them at the center of the island,
south of the town. It is called the <font color="LEVEL">Hills of Gold.</font>
 You can find there every monster that I've
mentioned. Before going there, though, visit 
Captain <font color="LEVEL">Zerstorer Marcela.</font> If you catch a
monster on Hills of Gold, he will reward you. I
 don't know what you're doing know. but it will
 benefit you.<br>
By the way, be careful of the Muertos who are
 wandering around Hills of Gold -- they are no
 easy target, whatever their appearance. Fight
 them only after you have reached level 11.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="13"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
Weapons are divided into 7 types: One-Handed
Sword, Two-Handed Sword, Blunt Weapon,
Dagger, Polearm, Fist and Bow. Among those,
let's first focus one the two Sword types, Blunt
Weapons, Dagger and Bow. If you are a Kamael,
listen especially carefully about the One-Handed
Sword, Two-Handed Sword, Blunt Weapons and
Bow.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 15">One-Handed Sword.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 16">One-Handed Blunt Weapon.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 17">Two-Handed Sword and Blunt Weapon.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 18">Dagger.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 19">Bow.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="6"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
When you reach level 10, visit <font color="LEVEL">Hierarch Kekropus</font>.
He will supervies a ceremony which is necessary
for you to become a true Kamael warrior.<br>
You should also meet <font color="LEVEL">Zerstorer Marcela</font>, whom
you can find at the town entrance. He has been
troubled by the increasing number of monsters
on Hills of Gold and may want your help to get
rid of the monsters.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="5"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
At this level, if you prefer to use a speceific attack
skill, train hard to enhance that skill. Upgrade the
ones you already use most when you become
level 10.<br>
As a rule, novices acquire an attack skill first and
only later learn support skills. Therefore, it may
be helpful to learn passive skills like <font color="LEVEL">Weapon
Mastery, Armor Mastery, Magic Immunity</font> or <font color="LEVEL">Soul
Mastery.</font> I also recommend that you learn <font color="LEVEL">Rapid
Attack,</font> which temporarily enhances your attack
power.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="15"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
The <font color="LEVEL">One-Handed Sword</font>is the most basic
 weapon in the game, prossessing balanced
attributes. The Squire's Sword you began your
adventures with was one of these. Unless you 
prefer a specific weapon. I recommend staying
with a One-Handed Sword.<br>
You can also use <font color="LEVEL">Fallen Atack</font> with it, which will
 allow you to strike a critical blow to enemies.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="19"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
<font color="LEVEL">Bow</font> is its ability to deliver damage at range. It is
 the slowest weapon, but can also infliict the
 greatest damage, making it ideal for support in
 combat. If you master the bow, however, it is
 possible to use it as your primary weapon.<br>
In addition, a bow can use a magical skill called
 <font color="LEVEL">Fallen Arrow</font>. All in all, it is a highly useful and
 versatile weapon.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
Which weapon do you use now? What kind of 
weapon do you want to use in the future? The
 reason why I'm asking this question is that it is
 important that you find the most suitable weapon
 for you when you reach level 6<br>
If you think that a Dagger is the best fit, buy a
 <font color="LEVEL">Bone Dagger</font>. If you have enough money, you
 can also buy a Doom Dagger, but a Bone Dagger 
should be good enough. If you prefer a Sword,
buy a <font color="LEVEL">Short Sword</font>. If you have enough money,
you can also buy a Broad Sword, but a Short
 Sword should be good enough. If you want to
 use a blunt weapon rather than a knife, I
 recommend a <font color="LEVEL">Club</font>. A blunt weapon has a higher
 accuracy rate than other weapons. A Lance,
meanwhile, can be used to attack serveral
 enemies at once, while a Bow is ideal for remote
attack.<br>
No matter which weapon you use, though, don't
forget this: you can use the Kamael's unique
weapon after reaching level 20 and completing
the first class transfer. If you are a Kamael male,
you must be familiar with the Two-Handed Sword
and the One-Handed Sword. If you are a Kamael
female, you should be familiar with the
One-Handed Sword and the Bow.<br>
You will have enough money to buy the next
 weapon once you reach level 9 or 10. But you'd
 better wait a while. As I mentioned if you take
 the test given by <font color="LEVEL">Hierarch Kekropus</font>, he will give 
you a weapon.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 13">"I'd like to know the characteristics of each weapon."</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 14">"I'd like to know about armor."</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="18"><![CDATA[<html><body>Newbie Guide:<br>
A<font color="LEVEL">Dagger</font> allows you to attack with unsurpassed
speed, as well as the greatest chance of
inflicting critical damage. However, its accuracy
 is low, its reach is quite short and even its critical
 damage is low compared to other weapons on
 the same level. A Dagger also has a very small
 range of random damage<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
