<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.BaseNPCController"
    id="32281" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Oracle Guide</name>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>MAGIC_CREATURE</race>
        <sex>MALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="1.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="42.0" radius="16.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>[You feel a chill and hear a voice...]<br>
Oracle Guide:<br>
A Demon who remained on the island gathered the most beautiful crystals he could find and cast a spell on them. As a result, they are now known as the Contaminated Crystals.<br>
[You see a building surrounded by a black fog in the spehere.]<br>
In this place, northwest of here, you will find the remains of the Demon. We do not know what is inside, since it was not built by materials native to the island, but I am sure there is a Contaminated Crystal hidden somewhere within the <font color="LEVEL">Darkcloud Mansion</font>.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest CrystalCaverns">Touch the sphere.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Oracle Guide:<br>
You see a once-beatiful room made of crystal and coral, filled with jewels, and surrounded by black watery.<br>
The Crystal Caverns, where Parme is being held captive, used to be a beautiful palace. However, it has been contaminated by the Demons, and they are the only beings able to enter.<br>
You can avoid them, however, by carrying a <font  color="LEVEL">Contaminated Crystal</font>, which will make you appear to be one of them. Do not overuse it, however, or it will lose its effectivness.<br>
Because of the danger, I cannot send you there if youre abilities are not sufficent to defend yourself against the Demons, or if you are alone.<br>
(In order to enter, you must be in a party whose members are level 78 or higher. Each member must possess their own Contaminated Crystal.)<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Ask about Contaminated Crystal</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest CrystalCaverns">Lay hands on the sphere.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Oracle Guide:<br>
A mysterious five-colored whirlwind swirls within an aquamarine sphere, and you hear a clear, cultured voice.<br>
Welcome. I am the first child of the Oracle. My mistress ia <font color="LEVEL">Parme</font>, the Shamaness of the Water Dragon. She is currently under the enemy's control, but an Oracle led me to this place just before she was captured.<br1>
My mission is to safely escort you to her current location.<br>
Unfortunately, that place is unreachable without proper preparation.<br>
If you are ready, please give me your hand, and I shall open the way.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask what you need to prepare.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest CrystalCaverns">Touch the sphere.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4390"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</npc>
