<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<npc type="" id="32548" xsi:schemaLocation="npc ../npc.xsd"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="npc" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="false">
        <name display="true" send="false">Keucereus</name>
        <title send="false">Admiral</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <sex>FEMALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="160.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="25.0" radius="12.5"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Keucereus:<br>
Are you an adventurer from Aden? Many of your comrades have already traveled here. I am truly grateful. Despite our lands' ancient hostility towards each other, it warms my heart to see these new bonds of friendship form between us. With your help, I hope to restore Gracia to its former glory...<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about the current situation in Gracia.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">Ask about the Seed.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">Ask about the occupation status of the Seed.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Keucereus:<br>
There are many things we do not understand about the Seed. What we do know is that its interior is vastly different from the continent on which we live. <br>We also know that its interior changes depending on who its lord is. In discussing the Seeds of Infinity and Destruction, think of the Seed of Infinity as a land of death controlled by undead lord and the Seed of Destruction as the land of Dragonkin controlled by the lord of Dragonkin. We are still attempting to learn more about the other Seeds, but we expect the same conditions apply.<br>
Since they appeared, even the topography of Gracia has been altered. The land has become poisonous, making it nearly impossible to move except via airship or Aurabird. We do not know if we can ever restore this land to its former state, but our immediate goal must be to defeat the lords of the Seeds. Once they have been vanquished, we can turn our attention to reclaiming our land.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Keucereus:<br>
Gracia is in a very precarious situation.<br>
After my father, King Paris, passed away, Gracia was engulfed in civil war. It finally ended, but the peace that followed was hardly complete. It was...a breathing space to llow the two sides to regain their strength.<br>
Before that happened, however, the Priests of Darkness appeared. We thought they were only legends from the ancient books. Even the worshippers of Shilen didn't think they really existed. If my father did know about them, then he obviously didn't consider them much of a threat. But the time we realized they were, it was too late...<br>Seeds spawned from the world of Death sprouted throughout Gracia, spawning dangerous monsters. Except for those I saved, I doubt anyone survived the assault. Apart from those blasted pagans, of course.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Keucereus:<br>
My military commander, General Dilios, will know the occupation status of the Seed. Ask him for the details.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 0">Back</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
</npc>
