<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<template:npc
    controller="com.l2jserver.model.world.npc.controller.NotImplementedNPCController"
    id="32323" xsi:schemaLocation="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc ../../npc.xsd"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:template="http://schemas.l2jserver2.com/npc">
    <info aggressive="false" targetable="true" attackable="true">
        <name display="true" send="false">Avant-Garde</name>
        <title send="false">Transformation Wizard</title>
        <level>70</level>
        <race>HUMAN</race>
        <sex>FEMALE</sex>
        <stats>
            <hp regen="7.5" max="2444.46819"/>
            <mp regen="2.7" max="1345.8"/>
            <attack critical="4" evasion="0" range="40">
                <physical speed="253.0" damage="688.86373"/>
                <magical speed="333.0" damage="470.40463"/>
            </attack>
            <defense>
                <physical value="295.91597"/>
                <magical value="216.53847"/>
            </defense>
            <move walk="50.0" run="120.0"/>
            <base wit="20" dex="30" men="20" con="43" str="40" int="21"/>
        </stats>
        <experience>0</experience>
        <sp>0</sp>
        <collision heigth="24.5" radius="8.0"/>
    </info>
    <talk default="default">
        <chat id="default"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
I am Avant-Garde, the Transformation Wizard. I have long wandered through the land and only recently settled here.<br>
In fact, my young friend, I am not a wizard of the Ivory Tower. You look surprised! Heh. Think of me as a wanderer who acquired a special power quite by chance... My magic, however, requires some very specialized items.<br>
If you have acquired these unique items from the dark wizard in Hardin's Academy, then perhaps I can help you.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Ask about transformation.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_TransformSkillList">Learn transformation.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_BuyTransform">Purchase items related to transformation.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest SubClassSkills">Learn about subclass certification.</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Quest">Quest.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="cantbuy"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
You must be able to transform in order to buy transformation-related goods.<br>
Find a great wizard who wields black magic and can open the path to transformation for you. The you may return here.
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="1"><![CDATA[<html><body>Wizard of Transformation Avant-Garde:<br>
What do you wish to know about transformation?<br><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 2">"What do I need to know about transformation?"</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 3">"What do I need to do to transform into another shape?"</a><br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 4">"What do I need to know before transformation?"</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="4"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
You must remember that once you have been transformed, you must not go into <font color="LEVEL">deep water</font>. Once you have reverted to your original form, your soul will need some time to recover -- you will not be able to transform again for some time. Understand?<br>
Other than that... Each individual soul contains its own <font color="LEVEL">unique character</font>. If you transform into something that matches that character, you may earn some benefits. Think of it as wearing a suit of clothes that fit you perfectly. Every race has its own respective "figure", so I advise you to do a little research about what kind of transformation would fit you best.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="cantlearn"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
This is not a path for every one. It is meaningless for me to even teach you Transformation until you have proven your ability.<br>
Meet the great wizard who uses black magic, open the road of Transformation, and then return to me.
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="2"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
To learn the magic of transformation, you will need to receive special training.<br>
Find the Wizard of Darkness, who lives at Hardin's Academy. He will open the path to transformation.<br>
You must have reached at least <font color="LEVEL">level 50</font> to embark on this path.<br>
You will also need a special seal. I do not know how you can obtain it, but without it transformation is impossible.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
        <chat id="3"><![CDATA[<html><body>Transformation Wizard Avant-Garde:<br>
After you have been guided through the process of transformation by a wizard, you may transform yourself into another shape by bringing a transform sealbook to me.<br>
Know that it is no easy task to earn one. I have heard, however, that you may find one through the Marketeer of Mammon or the Adventure Guild.<br>
<a action="bypass -h npc_%objectId%_Chat 1">Back.</a>
</body></html>]]></chat>
    </talk>
    <skills>
        <skill level="1" id="4045"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4408"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4409"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4410"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4411"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4412"/>
        <skill level="11" id="4413"/>
        <skill level="2" id="4414"/>
        <skill level="1" id="4415"/>
        <skill level="14" id="4416"/>
    </skills>
</template:npc>
